<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="inspirations">
        <item>\"The secret to having it all is knowing you already do\" \nUnknown</item>
        <item>\"Those who have the ability to be grateful are the ones who have the ability to achieve greatness\" \nSteve Maraboli</item>
        <item>\"We must find time to stop and thank the people who make a difference in our lives\" \nJohn F Kennedy</item>
        <item>\"This is a wonderful day. I\'ve never seen this day before\" \nMaya Angelou</item>
        <item>\"Be a rainbow in someone else\'s cloud\" \nMaya Angelou</item>
        <item>\"When we focus on our gratitude, the tide of disappointment goes out and the tide of love rushes in. \" \nKristin Armstrong</item>
        <item>\"Let us be grateful to the people who make us happy\" \nMarcel Proust</item>
        <item>\"A multitude of small delights constitutes happiness\" \nCharles Baudelaire</item>
        <item>\"Gratitude is the memory of the heart\" \nJean Baptiste Massieu</item>
        <item>\"All the great blessings of my life are present in my thoughts today\" \nPhoebe Cary</item>
        <item>\"The more you praise and celebrate your life, the more there is in life to celebrate\" \nOprah Winfrey</item>
        <item>\"Be thankful for what you have; you\'ll end up having more.\" \nOprah Winfrey</item>
        <item>\"We can only be said to be alive those moments when our hearts are conscious of their treasures\" \nThornton Wilder</item>
        <item>\"Know yourself to improve yourself\" \nAuguste Compte</item>
        <item>\"A quiet positive thought changed it all\" \nAvantik</item>
        <item>\"Gratitude opens your eyes to the limitless potential of the universe\" \nStephen Richards</item>
        <item>\"Enjoy the little things, for one day you may look back and realize they were the big things.\" \nRobert Brault</item>
        <item>\"Reflect upon your present blessings, of which every man has plenty; not on your past misfortunes, of which all men have some.\" \nCharles Dickens</item>
        <item>\"Acknowledging the good that you already have in your life is the foundation for all abundance.\" \nEckhart Tolle</item>
        <item>\"Gratitude is a currency that we can mint for ourselves, and spend without fear of bankruptcy.\" \nFred De Witt Van Amburgh</item>
        <item>\"He is a wise man who does not grieve for the things which he has not, but rejoices for those which he has.\" \nEpictetus</item>
        <item>\"When I started counting my blessings, my whole life turned around\" \nWillie Nelson</item>
        <item>\"The more grateful I am, the more beauty I see\" \nMary Davis</item>
        <item>\"There is a calmness to a life lived in gratitude, a quiet joy.\" \nRalph H. Blum</item>
        <item>\"The root of joy is gratefulness\" \nDavid Steindl-Rast</item>
        <item>\"Gratitude is the sign of noble souls\" \nAesop</item>
        <item>\"When you are grateful, fear disappears and abundance appears\" \nAnthony Robbins</item>
        <item>\"The essence of all beautiful art, all great art, is gratitude.\" \nFriedrich Nietzsche</item>
        <item>\"Wear gratitude like a cloak and it will feed every corner of your life\" \nRumi</item>
        <item>\"If the only prayer you ever say in your life is Thank You, it will be enough\" \nMeister Eckhart</item>
        <item>\"Gratitude turns what we have into enough\" \nMelody Beattie</item>
        <item>\"Give thanks for a little and you will find a lot\" \nHausa Proverb</item>
        <item>\"You only live once, but if you do it right, once is enough\" \nMae West</item>
        <item>\"When it comes to life the critical thing is whether you take things for granted or take them with gratitude\" \nG. K. Chesterton</item>
        <item>\"Feeling gratitude and not expressing it is like wrapping a present and not giving it\" \nWilliam Arthur Ward</item>
        <item>\"There are only two ways to live your life. One is as though nothing is a miracle. The other is as though everything is a miracle.\" \nAlbert Einstein</item>
        <item>\"Gratitude changes the pangs of memory into a tranquil joy\" \nDietrich Bonhoeffer</item>
        <item>\"Gratitude is riches. Complaint is poverty.\" \nDoris Day</item>
        <item>\"Gratitude is when memory is stored in the heart and not in the mind\" \nLionel Hampton</item>
        <item>\"Let us swell with gratitude and allow it to overwhelm us\" \nGrace Gealey</item>
        <item>\"Silent gratitude isn\'t very much to anyone\" \nGertrude Stein</item>
        <item>\"Fill the earth with your songs of gratitude\" \nCharles Spurgeon</item>
        <item>\"You cannot do a kindness too soon, for you never know when it will be too late\" \nRalph Waldo Emerson</item>
        <item>\"No one who achieves success does so without the help of others, the wise and confident acknowledge this help with gratitude\" \nAlfred North Whitehead</item>
        <item>\"Find the good and praise it\" \nAlex Haley</item>
        <item>\"Surprise is the seed of gratefulness. Become aware of surprises\" \nDavid Steindl-Rast</item>
        <item>\"Gratitude is happiness doubled by wonder\" \nG. K. Chesterton</item>
        <item>\"Gratitude is the fairest blossom which springs from the soul\" \nHenry Ward Beecher</item>
        <item>\"Happiness is not what makes us grateful. It is gratefulness that makes us happy.\" \nDavid Steindl-Rast</item>
        <item>\"Abundance is not something we acquire. It is something we tune into.\" \nWayne W Dyer</item>
        <item>\"Showing gratitude is one of the simplest yet most powerful things humans can do for each other\" \nRandy Pausch</item>
        <item>\"Make visible what, without you, might perhaps never have been seen\" \nRobert Bresson</item>
        <item>\"When you focus on the good, the good gets better\" \nAbraham Hicks</item>
        <item>\"Be generous in prosperity, and thankful in adversity\" \nBahá’u’lláh</item>
        <item>\"Gratitude is nothing if it\'s not felt\" \nJamie Varon</item>
        <item>\"Drink from the well of your self and begin again\" \nCharles Bukowski</item>
        <item>\"In the face of brokeness, gratitude has the power to heal. In the face of despair, gratitude has the power to bring hope.\" \nRobert A Emmons</item>
        <item>\"Gratitude is not only the greatest of the virtues, it is the parent of all the others\" \nMarcus Tullius Cicero</item>
        <item>\"Hold everything dear\" \nJohn Berger</item>
        <item>\"As long as you are living there is more ahead of you\" \nMorgan Harper Nichols</item>
        <item>\"I am worthy of the time it takes to do the things that heal my heart\" \nMorgan Harper Nichols</item>
        <item>\"Your heart is still beating and there is still room for healing\" \nMorgan Harper Nichols</item>
        <item>\"Choose celebration over comparison\" \nMorgan Harper Nichols</item>
        <item>\"Walk as if you are kissing the Earth with your feet.\" \nThich Nhat Hanh</item>
        <item>\"If I am not good to myself, how can I expect anyone else to be good to me?\" \nMaya Angelou</item>
        <item>\"No matter what happens, or how bad it seems today, life does go on, and it will be better tomorrow\" \nMaya Angelou</item>
        <item>\"If much has been denied me, much, very much, has been given me\" \nHelen Keller</item>
        <item>\"For love casts out fear, and gratitude can conquer pride\" \nLouisa May Alcott</item>
        <item>\"Embrace every new day with gratitude, hope and love\" \nLailah Gifty Akita</item>
        <item>\"Never let the things you want make you forget the things you have\" \nSanchita Pandey</item>
        <item>\"Usually, that which could have been better could have been worse\" \nMokokoma Mokhonoana</item>
        <item>\"The soul that gives thanks can find comfort in everything\" \nHannah Whitall Smith</item>
        <item>\"Living simply makes loving simple\" \nbell hooks</item>
        <item>\"Love is an action, never simply a feeling\" \nbell hooks</item>
        <item>\"There is light in darkness, you just have to find it\" \nbell hooks</item>
        <item>\"Our feelings are our most genuine paths to knowledge\" \nAudre Lorde</item>
        <item>\"At the end of the day, we can endure much more than we think we can\" \nFrida Kahlo</item>
        <item>\"Happiness is not something ready made. It comes from your own actions\" \nDalai Lama XIV</item>
        <item>\"We can never obtain peace in the outer world until we make peace with ourselves\" \nDalai Lama XIV</item>
        <item>\"Pain is inevitable. Suffering is optional\" \nHaruki Murakami</item>
        <item>\"We only have what we give\" \nIsabel Allende</item>
        <item>\"Write what should not be forgotten\" \nIsabel Allende</item>
        <item>\"You are the storyteller of your own life, and you can create your own legend, or not.\" \nIsabel Allende</item>
        <item>\"It\'s enough for me to be sure that you and I exist at this moment\" \nGabriel García Márquez</item>
        <item>\"There is always something left to love\" \nGabriel García Márquez</item>
        <item>\"If you see no reason to give thanks, the fault lies in yourself.\" \nTecumseh</item>
        <item>\"Gratitude is the direct way out of comparison.\" \nRobyn Conley Downs</item>
        <item>\"Optimism is a muscle that gets stronger with use\" \nRobin Roberts</item>
        <item>\"Do what moves you. Embrace what gives you stillness\" \nQ. Gibson</item>
        <item>\"Sit with your shallow parts and you will learn to survive the deepest tides\" \nQ. Gibson</item>
        <item>\"Come closer to yourself there\'s always room\" \nQ. Gibson</item>
        <item>\"My mind is a beautiful place, I water it well so that others can be fed from my garden\" \nQ. Gibson</item>
        <item>\"You are the sky. Everything else is just weather\" \nPema Chödrön</item>
        <item>\"Letting go of who I\'m not any longer, to make room for who I am\" \nLalah Delia</item>
        <item>\"Healing only works if you surrender to its process\" \nLalah Delia</item>
        <item>\"How liberating is it to pursue wholeness instead of perfection\" \nMorgan Harper Nichols</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>